<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Geo&#39;s Page on Geo&#39;s Page</title>
    <link>https://geoch.top/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Geo&#39;s Page on Geo&#39;s Page</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 23:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Posts</title>
      <link>https://geoch.top/posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geoch.top/posts/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://geoch.top/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geoch.top/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;profile&#34;&gt;PROFILE&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Name&lt;/strong&gt;: Changrui CHEN (陈常瑞)&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Institute Address&lt;/strong&gt;: College of Information Science and Engineering, Ocean University of China, No. 238 Songling Road, Qingdao, 266100 P.R. China&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;E-Mail&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;research-interests-and-statements&#34;&gt;RESEARCH INTERESTS AND STATEMENTS&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My research interests focus on object detection and segmentation in many application environments (e.g., drone-captured images, underwater images). I have developed two underwater robots to deploy and test our algorithms for the real-world application. Besides, I also interest in mining the relation in natural images to boost the deep learning segmentation algorithm under weakly supervised or unsupervised condition.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;education&#34;&gt;EDUCATION&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bachelor
Ocean University of China, Computer Science and Technology, 2013-2017&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Master
Ocean University of China, Vision Lab, Computer Technology, 2017-now&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;honors-and-awards&#34;&gt;HONORS AND AWARDS&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2019 IEEE International Conference on Computer Vision (ICCV) Vision Meets Drones Challenge&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Object Detection in Images: &lt;strong&gt;Runner-up&lt;/strong&gt; (Role: Leader)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2017 Underwater Robot Piking Contest (Organized by National Natural Science Foundation of China)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Object Detection(online): &lt;strong&gt;First Award&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2018 Underwater Robot Piking Contest&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Object Detection(offline): &lt;strong&gt;Second Award&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Object Picking: &lt;strong&gt;Third Award&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2017 China Computer Federation Ship Detection in the Complex Ocean Environment&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;First place in the preliminary round，Top 5% in the final round&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ocean University of China &lt;strong&gt;Outstanding Graduate Student&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;papers&#34;&gt;PAPERS&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[1] RRNet: A Hybrid Detector for Object Detection in Drone-captured Images, first author, accepted by &lt;em&gt;IEEE International Conference on Computer Vision Workshop (ICCVW 2019)&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[2] Learning Deep Relations to Promote Saliency Detection, first author, accepted by &lt;em&gt;Thirty-Fourth AAAI Conference on Artificial Intelligence (AAAI 2020) Oral&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[3] Exploring Ubiquitous Relations for Boosting Classification and Localizations, first author, &lt;em&gt;Knowledge-based Systems&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[4] Few-shot Learning for Domain-specific Fine-grained Image Classification, co-author, accepted by &lt;em&gt;IEEE Transactions on Industrial Electronics&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[5] Highlight Every Step: Knowledge Distillation via Collaborative Teaching, co-author, submitted to &lt;em&gt;IEEE Transaction on Cybernetics&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;research-projects&#34;&gt;RESEARCH PROJECTS&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[1]	Graduate Student Foundation of Ocean University of China: Object Detection in Complex Underwater Environment, March 2018 - March 2019 (Leader)&lt;br&gt;
[2] Student Research Development Project of Ocean University of China: A Medical Assistance Application based on Miband, 2016 (Leader)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>